healthfinder.gov 2005-12-31

# About healthfinder®: Privacy - healthfinder®

##  Home > About  healthfinder® > Privacy Policy 

healthfinder® is a free portal to reliable consumer health and human services information developed by the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. When you visit our Web site, we do not collect any information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us (other than information automatically collected and stored in the Web server's logs—see below). As a portal Web site, healthfinder® links to other Web sites, and once a user leaves the healthfinder® site to visit a linked site, the privacy policy of that site applies. 

###   
Personal Information

You do not have to provide any personal information to visit this Web site. 

If you choose to provide us with information about yourself through an e-mail message, form, survey, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication.

### Information Automatically Collected and Stored in Web Server Logs

When you browse through any Web site, certain personal information about you can be collected. Our Web server software automatically collects and temporarily stores the following information about each visit for statistical purposes:

  * the name of the domain you use to access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are using an America Online account, or stanford.edu, if you are connecting from Stanford University's domain) 
  * the date and time of the visit 
  * the pages visited 
  * the address of the Web site you came from when you came to visit

We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected about you.

### Disclosure

The [U.S. Department of Health and Human Services](http://www.hhs.gov/), of which the healthfinder® Web site is a part, does not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information about visitors, unless required for law enforcement or by statute.

### Intrusion Detection

This site is maintained by the U.S. Government. It is protected by various provisions of Title 18, U.S. Code. Violations of Title 18 are subject to criminal prosecution in federal court.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

### Systems of Records

Information originally collected in traditional paper systems can be submitted electronically, i.e., electronic commerce transactions and information updates about eligibility benefits. Electronically submitted information is maintained and destroyed pursuant to the Federal Records Act, and in some cases may be subject to the Privacy Act. If information that you submit is to be used in a Privacy Act system of records, there will be a Privacy Act Notice provided.

### IHC Disclosure Statement

healthfinder® also provides an IHC disclosure statement as recommended by the Science Panel on Interactive Communication and Health.

You may also wish to review our disclaimer.
